adoperationsonline.com 2012-12-30

# Privacy | Ad Operations Online

AdOperationsOnline.com values and respects your privacy. This statement sets out our privacy practices with respect to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information on this site.

This site may contain links that take you to other web sites. This privacy statement does not extend to the data collection practices of third parties and AdOperationsOnline.com does not assume any responsibility for the privacy practices, policies or actions of third parties. You should read the individual privacy policies of such sites and make an informed decision as to whether or not you wish to use these sites based on their privacy practices.

Personal information is information that is personally identifiable to you. Personal information may include your name, e-mail address and mailing address, as the case may be. Visitors of this web site are not requested to reveal any personal information. However, on a voluntary basis, you may provide and disclose personal information to us in using certain features of our site, such as the comments.

AdOperationsOnline.com will never disclose, sell or lease to any third party other than our affiliates, either free of charge or for remuneration, any personal information that you provide on this site without your permission, unless we are required to do so by law.

If you submit an e-mail inquiry or a comment to this site, any personal information you might submit at the same time will only be used by AdOperationsOnline.com administrators who need to have access to it in order to respond to your inquiry.

When your personal information is no longer required for the purposes for which it was initially collected or in accordance with other statutory requirements, the information will be destroyed within the next twelve (12) months.

In some cases, we collect information about you that is not personal information. Examples of such information include the type of Internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using and the domain name of the web site and/or Internet Service Provider through which you are linked to this site. Such visitor data may be used to improve the content of this web site and to help us determine which features and services are most important to its visitors.

This is done through the use of standard technology called cookies. Cookies are small data files that are downloaded and stored on your computer when you visit a particular web site. By assigning a unique data element to each visitor, the web site is then able to recognize repeat users, track usage patterns and better serve them when you go to a site. You may choose to disable cookies by turning them off in your browser. Consult your browser’s documentation to learn how to do this.

Your personal information is treated as private, confidential information by AdOperationsOnline.com and we strive to ensure that your personal information is protected at all times. To maintain the confidentiality of your personal information, this information is kept in a secure environment by AdOperationsOnline.com.

However, even though AdOperationsOnline.com has implemented methods designed to ensure the protection of your personal information that are considered to be effective, we cannot guarantee that such information will not be lost, used unlawfully or modified in a fraudulent manner since no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely confidential. Consequently, we bear no liability for the use that may be made of the information by you or any third party.

If you have already requested to be part of a mailing list, you may cancel your profile by going back to the section where you created that request or by contacting us using the information provided at the end of this privacy statement. If you have previously provided us with personal information and wish to verify it or have the information removed from our records or corrected, please contact us using the information provided at the end of this privacy statement.

AdOperationsOnline.com reserves the right to change this privacy statement as it sees fit and without prior notice. However, we will ensure that any change to this statement is in compliance with the laws in effect in the Republic of Ireland and the European Union with regard to this subject matter and posted on this page.

If you have any comments, questions or complaints regarding our privacy statement or practices, please [contact us](http://www.adoperationsonline.com/contact-adoperationsonlinecom/).
